After the first wave of artificial neural networks in the mid 80s,
上世纪 80 年代中叶掀起第一轮人工神经网络热潮后
it became clear that feedforward networks are
显然前馈网络存在缺点
limited since they are unable to capture temporal dependencies,
因为它们无法采集时间依赖
which, as we said before,
正如我们前面提到的
are dependencies that change over time.
即历经时间的依赖
Modeling temporal data is critical in most real-world applications,
在大多数现实世界的应用中 时态数据的建模很关键
since natural signals like speech and video have time
因为语音和视频等自然信号具有
varying properties and are characterized by having dependencies across time.
随着时间而变化的属性 具有依赖时间的特点
By the way, biological neural networks have recurring connections,
另外生物神经网络具有反复出现的连接
so applying recurrence to artificial feedforward neural networks made natural sense.
所以把循环应用到人工前馈神经网络中可以行得通
The first attempt to add memory to neural networks were the Time Delay Neural Networks,
首先向神经网络中添加存储的是时延神经网络
or TDNNs in short.
简称 TDNN
And TDNNs, inputs from past timesteps were introduced to the network input,
在网络输入中 时延神经网络中前期的输入也被引入到网络中
changing the actual external inputs.
改变实际外部输入
This had the advantage of clearly allowing
显然这样做的好处是
the network to look beyond the current timestep,
可以让网络不仅仅考虑当前的时间步长
but also introduce to clear disadvantage,
但同时也具有明显的劣势
since the temporal dependencies were limited to the window of the time chosen.
因为时间依赖受限于所选的时间窗口
Simple RNNs, also known as Elman networks and Jordan networks,
简单循环神经网络 又称 Elman 网络和 Jordan 网络
were next to follow.
是接下来的内容
We will talk about all those later in the lesson.
我们会在这节课后面探讨这些
It was recognized in the early 90s that all of these networks suffer from what we call,
上世纪 90 年代初人们认识到这些网络都存在所谓的
the vanishing gradient problem,
梯度消失问题
in which contributions of information decayed geometrically over time.
即信息的贡献随着时间出现几何级消失
So, capturing relationships that spanned
那么采集
more than eight or ten steps back was practically impossible.
超过 8 或 10 步长的关系实际上是不可能的
Despite the elegance of these networks,
虽然这些网络很精确
they all had this key flaw.
但是都具有这个关键缺点
We will discuss the vanishing gradient problem in detail later.
我们随后会详细讨论梯度消失问题
You can also find more information about this topic right after this video.
你也可以在这个视频下方找到这一话题的更多信息
In the mid 90s, Long Short-Term Memory cells,
90 年代中期 人们发明了长短期记忆单元
or LSTMs in short,
简称 LSTM
were invented to address this very problem.
解决这一问题
The key novelty in LSTMs was the idea that some signals,
长短期记忆网络的主要新颖之处在于一些信号
what we call state variables,
即所谓的状态变量
can be kept fixed by using gates,
可以通过使用 Gates 进行储存
and reintroduced or not at an appropriate time in the future.
并且在未来合适的时间里 通过门被重新引入到网络中
In this way, arbitrary time intervals can be represented,
因此任意时间间隔都可以体现出来
and temporal dependencies can be captured.
可以采集到时间依赖
Don't be alarmed by this sketch.
不要担心这个介绍
We will get into all of the LSTM details later in this lesson.
我们随后在这节课将详细介绍长短期记忆网络的所有内容
Variations on LSTMs such as Gated Recurrent Networks,
长短期记忆网络的变体包括门控循环网络
or GRUs in short,
简称 GRU
further refined this theme, and nowadays,
进一步完善了这一主题
represent another mainstream approach to realizing RNNs..
如今成为实现循环神经网络的另一大主流方法